CLINTON KWADWO KWEI OFOSU

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A Public Relations Officer of the GTUC-SRC 2019/2020 administration with a developed business acumen and broad experience across public relations, human resource management, marketing and advertising roles. I am Highly adaptable and a self-motivated leader with proven ability to manage diverse personalities, offering strong oratory skills and quipped with problem-solving strengths to identify solutions to challenging problems. My strengths are in people-oriented jobs such as human resource management, public relations and marketing. I quickly adapt quickly working with colleagues and customers of all background with versatile and adaptable in approach in team collaboration and problem-solving.

WORK HISTORY

Manager, 05/2016 to Current

Queens Corner Bar - Tesano, Ghana

- Addressed customer issues to ensure a swift and successful resolution.
- Supervised and trained 3 customer service team members to provide exceptional service throughout the entire experience.
- Recruited, hired and trained 3employees for the marketing and sales drinks and local foods to customers
- Extended existing customer relationships through extensive communication and tried-and-true marketing strategies.

Youth Ambassador , 08/2019 to 08/2020 Marie Stopes Ghana - Tesano, Ghana

- Responsibly managed the Youth project on avoidance and the curbing of Teenage Pregnancy, planning to ensure the consistent smooth running of the project.
- Maintained smooth operations of the project through effective and efficient deliverables and objectives;

COMMUNITY ENTRY AND AWARENESS CREATION
CREATING A YOUTH FRIENDLY ENVIRONMENT IN THE CLINIC
SOCIAL BEHAVIOURAL CHANGE COMMUNICATION (SBCC)
SKILLS ACQUISITION and ENTERPRENEURSHIP PARTNERSHIPS and
COLLABORATIONS

SRC-Public Relation Officer, 07/2019 to 08/2020 Ghana Technology University College - Tesano-Accra, Ghana

CONTACT

 Collaborate with other Associations under the SRC and also the Events and Communication team to devise public relations campaigns and coordinate with advertising.

Address: 2nd Mukose Street,
Tesano-Accra, Ghana 00233
Phone: 558062691 Email:
ofosuclinton86@gmail.com
https://www.linkedin.com/in/clint onofosu-0478b0185/
https://www.facebook.com/flame.
ofosu?_rdc=1&_rdr

SKILLS

- · Communications strategies
- Social media proficiency
- · Media contacts management
- Information gathering and analysis
- · Professional business writing
- PR strategy development
- Communication skills
- Strong verbal communication
- Team leadership
- · Microsoft Office
- · Motivational team player
- Conflict resolution
- Self-motivated
- · Powerful negotiator
- Attention to detail
- In consultation with the Executive Council, package information about the SRC and its programs and communicate the same to students, organizations, institutions, groups, other bodies or individuals who may require such information.

- In consultation with the Executive Council, design publicity programs for the purposes of marketing and publicizing the SRC and its programs or activities.
- Receive all visitors on behalf of the SRC and attend to their needs.
- In the absence of the Vice-President, coordinate all activities of committees and bodies set up or registered under this constitution.
- · Be the repository of dates, events and programs of the SRC
- Draft communications for routine releases and emergency response.
- Managed social media accounts by composing content, engaging with followers in comments, monitoring activities, and researching trends.

Data Entry Officer, 06/2016 to 08/2016 Vidya Bookstore - Osu, Ghana

- Used WordPress to enter over 5000 book cover content data over a period of 3 months.
- Supported Chief Operating Officer with daily operational functions.
- Supported management in improving operations and resolving issues to deliver top-notch customer service.
- Researched and updated all required materials needed for firm and partners.
- Monitored multiple databases to keep track of all company inventory.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business Administration, Human Resource Management, 2020

Ghana Technology University College - Tesano

- I am a student leader, an executive member of the Student Representative Council. I am the Public Relations Officer for the student body.
 - Award of 10,000 cedies from Marie Stopes Ghana to work on a project to curb teenage pregnancy at Aburi

CERTIFICATIONS

Basic Education Certificate Examination

West African Senior School Certificate Examination International Youth Fellowship on Mind Education

SHS, General Arts, 2016 Achimota Secondary School -

Achimota

- My elective subject were Literature, Government, Christian Religious Studies and History
- I was the assistant head of the Technologies and Logistics Club in my school.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Effective Communication Followed up and kept track of expected orders from the court and correspondence from opposing attorneys.
- Computer Proficiency Used Microsoft Excel to develop inventory tracking spreadsheets.
- Supervision Supervised team of three staff members.
- Creative Problem Solving: Resolved product issue through
 consumer testing.